igamemom.com 2019-06-10

# Privacy Policy

Thanks for visiting igamemom.com.  The privacy of our visitors is important to us.  This privacy policy tells you how we collect and use personal information at this site. By using this site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.

**Collection of Information**

We collect personally identifiable information, like names and email addresses when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology**

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed. Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: https://adssettings.google.com. You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: http://optout.networkadvertising.org. However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

We may use third party advertisements, such as Google AdSense, to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site.  This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and measure their effectiveness. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties. You can choose to disable or selectively turn off cookies in your browser settings if you prefer.

**For European Economic Area Residents**

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing. If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact AdThrive at info@adthrive.com. If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences icon. (Available in the EU.)

**Distribution of Information**

This site does not share visitors’ personally identifiable information to any third party for marketing purposes. We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place.

**Commitment to Data Security**

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized staff (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

**Comments Submitted to This Site**

Comments submitted to this website are the responsibility of the commenter. We reserve the right to remove or edit comments at our discretion. Site URLs (if provided) are published along with comments. E-mail addresses are required with the submission of comments but are not disclosed, unless the commenter deliberately does so him/herself by entering the e-mail address in the main comment box in addition to the box clearly labeled for the e-mail address.

iGameMom reserves the right to delete any comments that it deems not beneficial to the readership. This includes but is not limited to comments containing profanity, self-promotion, harrassment, threats, or spam of any sort.

**RSS and Email Subscriptions**

This website records information about how people access our RSS feeds, but does not collect any personal identifiable information from or about our RSS subscribers. This website’s feed services collect the e-mail addresses of individuals that subscribe to our RSS feed via e-mail. Individual information about subscribers to this website’s feed is held in strict confidence; we will not release or disclose any specific subscriber information under any circumstances, unless required by law. Aggregated information stripped of any personally identifiable information may be disclosed.

**Advertising**

This website uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

**External Links**

This site contains links to other websites not owned by the owner of this website. We will not, and cannot, control how your personal information is used on these other websites.

**Privacy Contact Information**

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us at [contact@igamemom.com](mailto:contact@igamemom.com)

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy.  Any changes to this policy will be posted.
